http://www.helixoft.com/common/privacy-statement.html

Follow Us RSS
Home » Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement of Helixoft
Information about our Organisation and Web site
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Helixoft.
We are based in Slovakia. Our principal activity is: Software development Our privacy policy covers Helixoft and its Web sites:
Organisation Name:
Helixoft
Address:
Tomasikova 14
City, Zip:
Presov 			, 			08001
Country:
Slovakia
Controller:
Helixoft
Web Sites:
http://www.helixoft.com
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our Web sites
Our Web sites also include a link to:
ShareIt! - software payment processor
Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors when they order our products.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.
We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.
To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please
click here
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.
If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.
We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.
We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.
Confidentiality / Security
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us, by sending an email whether we are keeping personal data about you.
Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an email, we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you,
within a week. Although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge.
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, whereappropriate, you may have the data:
rectified or amended
completed
We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy oftheir personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.
We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse toprovide you with a copy of your personal data.
Privacy Compliance
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.
There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.
We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with theprivacy instrument.
Privacy Support
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
Name:
Peter Macej
Email address :
click here
TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used
